It's Alamoron
The toothless pterosaur was flying in the sky!
Look, it's a spiny dragon!
That's awesome!
It's a triceratops.
So cool
Baba baba baba baba baba
Why are you suddenly calling Daddy?
Tyrannosaurus rex
Do-do-do-do Doraemon
Is it okay?
Nobita, is everything all right?
Hey, hey, what are you afraid of?
How can there be real dinosaurs?
It's hard to say.
What are you talking about?
Somewhere in this world, there might still be dinosaurs alive.
So, Nobita...
Dinosaurs disappeared 66 million years ago.
Why
The Earth was hit by a huge meteorite and the dinosaurs became extinct.
How could
It's huge!
That's great
That's a flake dragon.
Nobita
Huh
It seems to have something
Where is it? Where is it?
That's it.
This is a fossilized dinoflagellate
It's great!
That's great, Fat Tiger.
Let me see
The fossil you found, you can take it back.
Last 5 years
Many dinosaur fossils have been found in Japan
Japan may have been a dinosaur kingdom.
Excuse me, is this a dinosaur fossil?
That's impressive.
No doubt it's a dinosaur's
No way!
How could Nobita find the fossil of a dinosaur
What's a fossil?
I'm here to announce
Not some fossil. I'm going to find a living dinosaur and show you.
Nobita
Okay, I'm recording.
What are you going to do if you don't find it?
What do you do?
Here we go again.
How exciting!
The video of the evidence was also well captured
Wait for me.
I'll find a live dinosaur and leave those guys speechless.
In the world
There are still many undiscovered dinosaurs
That should have existed in the course of evolution, but were not discovered.
It hurts.
A new dinosaur buried in a transitional fossil like that
Perhaps it's up to you to discover it.
At that time
it will be possible to name the dinosaur after you
Doraemon Doraemon
doraemon doraemon doraemon doraemon
Doraemon
Doraemon: Nobita's New Dinosaur
Dinosaur eggs?
Oh, you're so
Naive or innocent, I should say.
Give me back this shape, this size
It's a dinosaur egg from any angle.
Such naivety.
It's a good thing that you say it's a good thing that you are
But then
How do you know it's a dinosaur egg?
It could just be an ordinary stone.
Even if it's a fossil, it could be the fruit of an ancient tree.
00:08:21,790 It could be the poop of an archaic rhinoceros.
It's a bit of a bummer.
So
Just to be sure, take out the time wrap.
If you wrap it in a time wrap and rewind time
you will be able to tell if this is a dinosaur egg or not
It's not.
What are you going to do if it's really a dinosaur's egg after doing that?
I'll keep it.
It's too hard for Nobita
Why
It's not as easy as you think
And raising dinosaurs in a world where they're extinct
Before thinking about that kind of thing like a dream
Learn how to take care of yourself first
Give me back my gumbo!
That means Doraemon believes it's a dinosaur egg, too.
No, it's not.
If you don't believe me, take out the time wrapper.
It'll just end up as shit anyway
Time wrapped towel
That's fine
I can't wait!
Could it be a Triceratops or a Brachiosaurus?
I told you it's the poop of an Archaeopteryx.
I don't know, it could be a Tyrannosaurus.
Mum, what's for dinner today?
Huh? Nothing's changed.
Sure enough, it's probably just an ordinary stone.
Nobita also needs to sleep well
Good night
Nobita, get up!
It's itchy, Doraemon
Glasses Glasses
What's up, Nobita?
Do Doraemon
No, not sure it's a dinosaur yet.
It's going to be born
Gotta get the hot water going
Ambulance. Ambulance. And... and...
It's a dinosaur.
So cute.
Huh
Do... Doraemon.
Double Yolk Egg
How rare!
Thanks to the time wrapped scarf
The twin dinosaurs inside the egg grow up
Slow down. It's dangerous.
That's great. You can walk already.
This child won't come out.
Look, it's not scary. Come on out.
So warm
So, your name is Khoo.
And you are Mew
Kew and Mew?
It's got little feathers. It's lovely.
What kind of dinosaur is this?
Let's investigate
The Complete Encyclopedia of the Universe
Speaking of dinosaurs with feathers
Dinosaur and also Chironomus
Not this one. Not this one either.
Oops
How can
This dinosaur has not been recorded
It must be a new species of dinosaur.
If that's the case, it's a big find.
Name it Nobita Dinosaur
But, Nobita, you can't keep them here.
If Mom or anyone else finds out, it'll be a big deal.
No, I want to keep it.
I'll show them to Fat Tiger and Little Husband when they're old enough.
And leave them speechless
Please, Doraemon, can you just grow a little bit bigger?
Really, really cute.
Look at that. Isn't that nice?
You can only keep them until they grow up.
Great!
Please tell me more, Mew.
I'm full
What's wrong? You're eating so fast.
Dad
Thank you
Nobita, you've left the green peppers again, haven't you?
I ate it.
Mum, I'll have another bowl of miso soup too.
Okay, okay.
Eh, there's a lot left.
It's not good to be a picky eater.
I'm full
You're hungry, aren't you? Come on, eat.
Eat up eat up
Come on, Kew, eat too.
Not eating?
It's obviously so tasty
So, this
Ming Miao will eat
Kew if you don't eat properly
What's wrong?
I don't care
Hello?
You said you wanted to keep them, but you said so yourself, Nobita!
I feel like you guys are so much alike
Who are you talking about and who are you talking about?
Because Nobita is just like their parents.
We have to think of more ways
What do dinosaurs eat anyway?
What kind of place do they live in?
It's a fossilized plant.
It's beautiful.
Hello
Please teach me how to keep dinosaurs
How to breed
What kind of nest to sleep in, what kind of food to eat, etc.
That's it.
When it comes to dinosaurs, there are also carnivorous and herbivorous species.
Also related to how it lived
For example
Although like a lizard
But with feathers
So, why don't we find out what lizards and birds eat?
Do they live near the mountains or do they live near the sea?
In this case the food would be different again
Oh, a dinosaur with feathers.
Nobita, little Dora, time to eat
Today it's sashimi with tuna
I had a nice tuna today, so I went for the luxury
This is what Nobita likes to eat
I'm on.
I'm on
Eat up
It's delicious. Eat up.
No?
Eaten
That's good, that's good. One more.
Oh, that's good.
It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Really, Khoo.
Good pain, good pain, good pain
It's not good
Nobita
What's wrong with you? It's so late.
How can I cure the dinosaur?
Please
I checked it with the medical kit
It should get better.
Come on, Khoo.
Seems to have fallen asleep
Nobita, go to sleep too!
Good boy. Good boy.
Kew
I'm going out
Late. Late.
Nobe, look what time it is!
You go and stand in the corridor.
Yamada
Kawamura
Izumo Sugi
Nobe Nobe Nobuo
I'm calling you.
What the hell!
to to
Sending you yesterday's question paper
It's not 0 marks
What kind of guy is happy with 3 points?
Win!
That's good. Keep it up.
Come on, Nobita.
Come on, Nobita!
Come on, one more time.
Very good
Not even close.
That's it.
Oh, it's great to have Nobita on the bottom
It's really great
I feel a little bit more confident.
It's true
Hm
When you've seen grown up Kew and Mew
Don't cry afterwards
I'm back
Xiao Qiu Xiao Miao
Welcome home
Did Mew just fly?
Yes, I was shocked too.
Khoo, Khoo, fly over here too.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
But... it hurts.
It's only a matter of time before mum finds out.
Why? Can't you do anything about it?
Yes, I'll look for it.
Diorama set for breeding
This is a diorama for keeping animals or bugs
Diorama?
First decide on the terrain
That's about right, isn't it?
Then it's with this
In the words of the fast miniatures manufacturing camera
No matter what it is, it can be turned into a small part.
You can arrange them freely inside
awesome
But... it's going to be discovered.
Don't worry, it's here.
With size adjustment
Size can also be adjusted freely
And then, if you reduce the size with the reduction light
Really wide
What's up, Nobita?
If people are here, no one can find them.
Okay, I've decided to build one here just for us.
Nobe Dinosaur Land.
Yoo-hoo
Wrong! Do the math again!
It's so noisy!
This way. This way.
Maths homework is difficult
That's right, it's really hard
Hey Nobita
Did you find the dinosaur?
Than practising the bar flip
How about practising chewing peanuts with your eyes?
No more practice
It doesn't bother me if I can't do this kind of thing
This is a safe place.
I'm coming too. I'm coming too!
This is it!
Do it, do it!
Mew, that's great!
In that case, I want them to be able to soar under the blue sky
That's fine.
This diorama has a weather adjustment function
What about, for example
Come on, it's Kew next.
A slide?
I think this should allow Kew to practice flying
That's right
Come on, Kew. Come here.
Right now
Is that okay?
Let's try again. With practice.
You'll be able to fly like a mu
It doesn't seem to like it
You can't do that. It just failed once.
If that happens, you won't be able to support yourself for long.
How dare you say such things, Nobita!
What a mouthful
It seems to be saying that it's OK to have this
Really
But why can't Kew fly?
It obviously looks exactly the same
Speaking of which, Mew's tail is a bit longer
Kew's tail is much shorter
Really!
And
Kew is much smaller than Mew
I didn't realise I'd grown up so much
It's time to...
I understand
What was it that Nobita said would be important
That goes without saying.
Definitely no dinosaurs to be found
Performing the peanut chewing with the eyes as promised
Show us
What is it? What is it? What is it?
What is this? What is this?
It's a real dinosaur.
This one is even better with all the fat!
Bastard, that's what a friend should say!
Me, me, me... I'm skinny as a bone.
I can't believe I'm eating peanuts
Nobita what the hell is going on here?
This is the new dinosaur I found, Nobita Dinosaur.
This is Khoo. That's Mew over there.
Don't be afraid
All three of them are my good friends
I'm so sorry.
What's that scream?
Nobita
Oh no, it's Mom. Doraemon.
No problem.
Reducing the light
Why is it a can of locusts
That's strange.
Anything is good. Get it out.
That's it.
Space Mobile Crayon
Use this red crayon to circle the range
You can then move to the position circled by the white crayon
Don't illustrate at this point
Maharishi
Nobita
Hello, Auntie
Beautiful today too.
I've been hearing barks lately
There's also inexplicably less food in the fridge
Did you have kittens and puppies in the house
I swear I don't have a cat or a dog
Is that so?
That's weird.
If it's actually a dinosaur that's being raised
Oh no.
Mum! Is that a dinosaur?
It's true. It's a dinosaur no matter how you look at it.
Do... Doraemon.
Gone
Where the hell did it go?
All right, next up is Kew.
You've both grown so much
Nobita
It is no longer possible to continue to feed them in this era
Mew is already higher than me.
For them
Wouldn't it be better to live with your mates
But where do we send them back to?
Back to the time when they existed, right?
If you work backwards from the time spent on the Time Wrapper
is from the late Cretaceous
Go to that time with a time machine
Let Kew and Mew return to their companions
I don't want it!
Absolutely not!
Nobita
Nobita I understand that it hurts to be apart
But you can't stay together forever
This wasn't their world in the first place.
But Kew can't fly yet.
If we send it back to the age of dinosaurs, it's not going to survive!
But that's the principle
We can't change history
And if you grow with your companions
Kew can definitely fly too
So, Nobita
Tomorrow. Tomorrow, the two of us.
Let's send Kew and Mew back to the Cretaceous
Okay, it's late. Let's go back.
This kind of thing
Of course I understand
Well done. Well done.
Maharishi
Khoo and Mew
I was born from the egg because of my caprice
So I had to protect them.
Let's go. To the Cretaceous!
Go in search of Kew and Mew's companions
Nobita!
Fat Tiger, Little Fu, Shizuka
That costume is going to
You were planning to go to the Cretaceous anyway!
You're not going to leave us behind, are you?
I'd like to come along too
If I can be of any help, just ask.
Guys
Everybody, are you ready?
Sure.
The heart is beating
Departure
To the Cretaceous
Engine start
Battery charge 1200%
Time space navigation system fully operational
Destination 66 million years ago in Cretaceous Japan
Hold on tight, folks!
Doraemon Where are we now?
About 600 years ago
6,000 years ago
It was the time when the Egyptian civilization of the Nile Valley flourished
I know this one.
Time of the birth of man
It was about 2.5 million years ago
And the Cretaceous period we're going to is
More than 60 million years ago
Now about one ten thousandth of a mile away
One ten thousandth
You'll have to wait in here a little longer.
There will be occasional shaking, so hold on tight
Doraemon This is the Cretaceous Period?
Well, we've gone back 66 million years.
Okay, let's go.
Wait!
We're going to the Cretaceous later. The temperature is very different from now.
00:38:05,690 and the concentration of oxygen was also different than in our time
And so?
Expedition set
This suit is waterproof, windproof and coldproof in every way
It can be adapted to a wide variety of environments and thus protects itself
It feels like an expedition now.
Super suitable
So let's go
This is Japan in the Cretaceous period
Come out
This is your hometown!
What is it?
Next, so that we don't get separated.
Locating the square scarf
Put this scarf around your neck like this
This button is the signal transmitter
When expanded, it becomes a map
This way we know where each other are at all times
Does that work?
So cute
Mew wants to put it on too, right?
We're the same colour
Kew also wears
That's good.
Then set off in search of Qiu and Miao's companions
I'll be the first to find them.
Me too
Why can't I see dinosaurs anywhere?
You're so ignorant, Fat Tiger. This is Japan.
How can there be large dinosaurs?
What's wrong, fat tiger?
What's the matter?
This way
Wait, Fat Tiger.
JD Dragon
It's a real dinosaur
Won't they attack us?
Stegosaurus is a herbivore
So just get close to it and you won't have any problems
To be precise, they're close relatives of Stegosaurus.
So it's true. There were many dinosaurs in Japan.
But something doesn't feel right.
What do you mean?
Isn't Stegosaurus a Jurassic dinosaur?
Indeed, Stegosaurus is a Jurassic dinosaur.
If that's the case, this is 100 million years older than the Cretaceous.
Jurassic is correct.
100 million years
But it shouldn't be
Does it mean that
Isn't that an Allosaurus that lived in the Jurassic?
It's not the Cretaceous period.
It's the Jurassic
But why would
Sorry
I may have accidentally pressed the wrong destination for the time machine
What the hell are you doing, Nobita?
You nerd
Everybody run full speed back to the time machine
Run!
Nobita, come on!
Wait for me
Run away!
Nobita, come on!
Wait for me
Quick
Went to the Cretaceous?
Call Dr. Gill.
So crowded
Nobita, what about the diorama set?
I just lost it.
Really, what can I say about you?
You're not going to get it wrong this time, are you?
Yes.
No mistake. This is Cretaceous Japan.
That's great. That's great!
Doraemon It must be here!
Nobita, Shizuka, Kew and Mew are counting on you.
Okay, let's go!
Come on, Kew.
Little Mew
This is Japan in the Cretaceous period
To be precise, the islands of Japan were not yet formed at this time.
It is still part of a huge continent
Look over there!
That's awesome!
It's the real Alamosaurus
This is too big
Look over there.
That's awesome
It's like a dinosaur kingdom
Is this the home of Kew and Mew?
Flight practice Flight practice
Kew's not a birdie. Don't give him a hard time. All right, let's go.
Sorry sorry sorry
Say it's this way!
You know what?
How can
What a beautiful lake
Look around here
Why can't I see dinosaurs anywhere?
Are they extinct?
How is that possible?
It's difficult because it's a new dinosaur, so there's no habitat in the database.
What are the clues?
Yeah.
Footprint stamp
Footprint stamp?
Kew, come here.
Lend me your feet for a while
Ready
What is this
It's a footprint.
If you stamp the ground like this
A footprint of the same shape will glow
I can't believe there are so many footprints
This is it.
Look, these footprints are all going in the same direction.
It must be a mass migration.
But why is that?
Report the number!
Doraemon What's this?
Egg Expedition
They'll help us find the footprints
So cute
I'm counting on you then
This is not edible
Is it really okay?
Stop talking nonsense and get after it!
No, it'll be dangerous if we fall behind.
Let's camp here today
Camping Balloon
Sleep in this tonight
This way. This way.
There are rooms for everyone. Choose your favourite.
That's great. I'll take this one.
It's so slick.
Soft
Awesome
Great
And what else?
Raise the balloon like this
And you won't be attacked by the beast!
That's great!
Unbelievable, isn't it?
We are now, 66 million years ago.
What a great meteor shower!
There are monkeys in this era?
It's not surprising if there were
Of course, I'm keeping an eye on them.
Got it. What do we do?
Catch them now?
A little more observation
Understand
Surely a new dinosaur
Why
Information about footprints came in from the egg expedition
Where exactly are they heading?
Anyway, let's go.
Okay, everybody, don't get separated.
All right?
Is it true that you passed through here?
What's wrong, Kew?
Doraemon Back!
Yes, it's a toothless pterodactyl.
No, this is their lair.
Everybody, run away at full speed.
Kew
Doraemon
Do these guys want to eat us?
This is better.
Is this what friends do?
No, no, they're not here to attack us.
It looks like they're in a panic because they've been scared by something.
We're saved!
Doraemon Here are the footprints
Really
Egg Expedition
Footprints continue in front of this
Thank you for your hard work
This is not edible
Be careful, everyone!
There's no telling what kind of dinosaurs are lurking around here.
How so
Dora, don't scare us!
You'll save us if we're in danger, right?
Whatever it is that's coming
My lord would have sent it flying
Rats are scary. Rats are scary.
Oh, really. Don't make a fuss.
There are animals like rats in this day and age.
Are you hungry, fat tiger?
It's not me
Want some chewing gum?
I told you it wasn't me.
Baba Baba Baba...
What's with the dad again?
Tyrannosaurus rex!
Look here
Momotaro Rice Ball
Broken
Cannot be eaten
Nothing else? Nothing else?
There you are. Chocolate partner.
Chocolate at a time like this
Divide this chocolate into two before giving it to the others
Then you can become friends with each other
is now
not possible
I'm not a civet
There should be more
Somebody help!
I'll take care of that.
It's so easy.
What's going on?
What are you doing? Let go!
Pain, pain, pain
Really? Your name is Gale.
Great, Fat Tiger.
That's awesome!
Everyone, let me introduce you
My friend from the heart, Gail
That's nice, Fat Tiger.
Sharing partner chocolates with each other after becoming partners
You can acquire each other's characteristics and abilities within one hour
If you become friends with a dinosaur
Good idea.
Let's all become friends with our favourite dinosaur
That's great!
Dinosaur sauce. Dinosaur sauce.
With
I want to be friends with little Mew
Same as Mew
If you don't mind, can you be my friend?
That's awesome.
Let's do it too
We're going, Kew.
Let's fly
Pain, pain, pain, pain
The flightless Qiu and Nobita are a perfect match
Triceratops
Only one horn. It must be one of its kind.
It's called a trophy.
Please tell me more, Topper.
A friend of a friend is also a good friend
It's okay.
One day, Kew will fly too.
Although I'm not qualified to say that either
Everyone, let's go!
And then
It's the sea.
The footprints have disappeared
There are many footprints
Good work, everyone
It seems that the footprints break off here
Where the hell did it go?
It didn't fall into the sea, did it?
It can't be
It must be around here.
Then let's split up and look for it.
That's too dangerous.
What's the matter, little Dora? Are you scared?
We have Gale and Topper with us.
All right then.
But be careful
In case it doesn't work in the middle of the day, take this with you
We'll use the scarf to confirm each other's positions
I see
Let's go too
Fat Fat Tiger These are
Are they all dinosaur skeletons?
Let's go back.
What are you afraid of?
What's wrong? Even Gale is like that.
Topper too, like he's afraid of something.
And I feel like I've been watched since a while ago.
See, Fat Tiger?
Let's go after it
Uh-huh.
Gere and Topper are waiting for us right here.
Don't worry about it.
We'll be right back
Junior Expedition Departure Follow Me Purple Team
Purple crew?
This is
Cretaceous actually existed in this kind of place
Some bad guys would poach dinosaurs and sell them for a high price
I've heard Doraemon say that before
Okay, let's both find out.
Let's go, purple team.
If I'm purple, what's a fat tiger?
The captain is red of course
Not orange
Don't let me hear the word orange again
Yes Red
Hey, look at this!
This is
Similar to Kew and Mew
Found it! Catch it!
Wait for me!
Sure enough it's that monkey
Very good. Go on, purple.
Why me?
Red as captain should take the lead at times like this
Scouting is a subordinate's job, isn't it? Come on, purple.
No, no, no. Red please.
Purple
Red
You're a bit noisy, aren't you?
It's orange
Old Mother
Mum
Really
What a brave expedition
The Monkey Speaks
You... You saved us, didn't you?
Half right
Yes Yes people
However, the other half of the answer is wrong
Sure enough all the footprints disappeared off the coast
Little Dora
What's this one?
Is that a footprint of something?
No, if it is, it's too big.
What's wrong, Mew?
Qiu
Do-Do-Do Doraemon
So Big
Everyone, use the bamboo dragonfly to escape!
Xiao Qiu
Fly up, Khoo
Fly Up
Nobita
Flying up Khoo is flying up
Da Xiong
Nobita
Qiu
Kew
Open Door
Bastard! Let us out!
Where's this ship going?
How do I know about such things
Is everything okay, Fat Tiger?
Damn it, can't I?
If it had such sharp teeth it would have broken the lock
There is still this solution
O Friend of the Heart
No mistake, it's Nobita's signal
Must have been swept away by the current
Little Dora, Nobita, he must be okay.
The expedition set should protect him, right?
Nobita
Good Boy
Here
How did we get saved?
Can we climb up?
Nobita
Doraemon
Great, you're all right.
Nobita
Shizuka
I'm so worried about you
It's really good that you're okay
But... what is this island?
I just saw a dinosaur that looks exactly like Kew and Mew
So, here's the new dinosaur...
What are you going to do?
It looks like they've reached the island too.
That's pretty good.
You're really taking it in stride
That island is a decisive place for the planet
If anything changes because of them
I understand everything
Already caught two of them
Hurry up and get away!
How can I go back after being screwed so badly?
But why this island?
The new alternative dinosaurs are the underdogs, forced into a life on the move
Finally cornered on a cliff by the sea
And from there gliding all the way to the island
Achieved a solitary boom
Even so, the island is still a mystery
It looks like it leads to a very deep place
Kew, wait!
What's wrong?
So that was
Go after it
Little Mew
Let's go too
Quickly Khoo
So spectacular
Look!
Mew is already with them
Qiu, they are your companions
Go on!
No, the battery is dead.
Is it okay?
Qiu
Stop it, Mew!
That's too much
Khoo too
Qiu is also your partner
Why
That's because
Because it can't fly?
Because it's small?
Because of the short tail?
In that case I would definitely
Help Kew learn to fly
Nobita
Not much time left before meteorite impact
It's almost time to get the kids under control
Otherwise everyone could be buried here
will die?
Can you wait a little longer?
This new dinosaur is slightly different from all the individuals so far
And, about the enigmatic island
However, if we have less than two hours left, we'll be on the island too.
I see
Try again. Don't be afraid.
This is not working
Whether mu or other similar
Neither will flutter their wings like that
One more time
That's not how you fly. Why can't you do it?
I'm sure you can do it too.
Just a little more effort
Qiu
Fool
Nobita
What just happened
If Kew wants to survive in this world
you must learn to fly
But I'm not really in a position to say such things
I can't do either the race or the test or the bar.
No such thing
Nobita knows the pain and sorrow of others
and can give companionship and dependence
This is the kind of Nobita I like
01:17:35,020
Khoo must be waiting for Nobita too
Thank you, Shizuka.
Here
Seeker's Cane
Thanks a lot
Looks like we've reached the island
Let's get out of here while we still can, Fat Tiger.
Fat Tiger
Come on, Purple
Do you want to continue investigating here?
Look at this!
I mean, you don't look like an explorer, you look like a thief.
Who the hell are those guys?
Is this a thumbnail sketch of the island?
I feel like I've seen it somewhere before
Could this island be
We need to inform everyone quickly
I'm sorry for saying such a mean thing.
I obviously can't even do one thing myself
But one day I'm going to learn how to flip a bar too
So, Khoo too
Don't give up so easily, Khoo too
That's the deal between us
Meteor
Little Dora The one just now was
This can't be
Little Dora, this is
How could I be so stupid?
I can't believe I didn't even notice such a thing
Doraemon
Shizuka
Fat Tiger
Little Husband
I'm glad you got here safely.
What the hell just happened compared to this?
Does it mean that this is
Nobita
Gentlemen
Doraemon What the hell is going on here?
This is exactly 66 million years ago.
as expected
So that was a meteorite that just fell?
No way.
Meteorite crashes into Yucatan Peninsula, Mexico
The meteorite stirred up dust that would have spread over the whole earth
What would be the result of that?
There's no danger on this side, is there?
Mexico is on the far side of the world, isn't it?
Dust from the fall of a giant meteorite
It will be accompanied by a heat wave sweeping the world
Burning everything on the surface of the earth to the ground
After this the cumulus clouds will block out the sun for a long time
The temperature of the Earth is thus lowered
The dinosaur metropolis
Don't
I can't believe it's going to end like this
But Doraemon will find a way to solve the problem, right?
Just like it always does
Sorry Nobita
I Can't Change History
Nobita
Nobita, stop it!
No. What do you want to do?
This is it
That's the reversing clock.
Give it back to me!
Little Dora
I'm going to use it to reverse time and send the meteor back into the universe
Stop it, Nobita!
This is the end
Time Patrol
Now leave the two new dinosaurs over there immediately
Boarding Time Ship
Otherwise you will be arrested for time crimes
Arrested?
Fat Tiger
In other words
Sorry for the bad memories
01:24:24,930 To prevent history from being changed, we have been monitoring the times
I say, can't we really help Kew and Mew?
I've been studying dinosaurs for a long time because I like them too
I can understand how you feel
1,000
But, sorry, we can't do anything to save them.
This is too cruel
The falsification of history must not be allowed
If you stop the meteor from falling, it's not just you.
None of you will ever be born
How can this be
The mammals only flourished when the dinosaurs died out
And that's how humans came to be
I'm not going to save you from death
I could never do such a thing
I want to reverse time and send the meteor back to the universe
Can't do it, Nobita.
Keep him under control
Be honest with me
Stop it!
Got him under control.
I want to protect Khoo and Mew
Stop
What's wrong with this guy?
This guy
We're here to help too
I'm not going to let you arrest Nobita
Nobita is just trying to protect Khoo and Mew
Mum
Only a few hours left before the heatwave arrives here
Get everyone out of here.
One moment
Can you give me a little more time?
Stop it, Jill. Everyone will be burned to the ground.
What
Untie the boy!
Don't interfere with anything they do
What the hell is going on here, Jill?
sure enough
as you can see
We cannot interfere with their actions
How about witnessing the moment when history is made
01:26:42,860 What about the Time Patrol? They're not approaching us.
What the hell is going on here?
The guy using is checking the card
Will react in case history is about to be rewritten
That it reacted to Nobita and Kew would mean
I can't imagine this kind of teenager who has the word ordinary written on his face
How to Change History
Pingfan is still really sorry for you
But Nobita was so handsome just now
No, I'm trying my hardest
So what should we do next?
That would be to save the dinosaurs, naturally
But how do we do it?
About that, right, Fat Tiger?
That's right, our Junior Expedition.
We've made a big discovery
It's better to see than to hear
What the hell is going on?
Look at that mountain. Does it look familiar?
Like what?
That's what I thought before
It feels like a slide on that hill
In that case
Then this is
Single Pole
This is
Tyre Jumper
This hill has three holes
I see
This is the concrete pipe in the open space
Then here is
Maharishi
There's no mistake, this is
Nobe Dinosaur Land
I can't believe it's written as Inuyasha again
No doubt it's Nobita's handwriting
The dinosaurs' lair is actually a climbing frame
I see
Device dropped in the Jurassic damaged the size adjustment
got bigger between 100 million years
And so in the long years
It became just like an island of nature ah
That's right.
If the island is a diorama set, then it has a weather adjustment function
It should protect the dinosaurs from outside disasters
Awesome
But what about the dinosaurs off the island?
Then
Can we use that prop?
The prop that moved Qiu and Miao to the roof
There's still this one
And this?
That means space moving crayon
Fat Tiger, Xiao Fu, Shizuka, Miao
You go to the mainland outside the island
Gather the dinosaurs in one place as far as you can
Use this red crayon to draw a circle around them
Nobita Khoo and I will
Drawing a circle around the island with a white crayon
Press this button when you have finished drawing
Move all the dinosaurs from outside the island to here
Awesome
This way everyone is saved
Great, Khoo Mew!
But time is running out
Let's finish before the heatwave hits, although it's extremely dangerous
But we still have hope
Okay, let's do it.
Okay, let's start the battle to save the dinosaurs.
They're acting a little suspicious.
If something goes wrong, can you take responsibility for it?
This could become
A decisive moment in the evolutionary history of living things
Can we wait a little longer?
One more hour
Take them away when the time is up
Got it
Let's go too
Kew is waiting here
There are no more working bamboo dragonflies
It doesn't matter, Kew will be able to fly too.
I thought we had a date
Let's go Nobita
Enclose the whole island as large as possible
Danger
It's that guy again
Why is it here
Flying away
Over there is the dinosaurs' lair
Oh no, Nobita continues to draw down
Doraemon
I can't believe it's not working
so big
That one is
It's too dangerous, isn't it?
Is it coming?
Shizuka drawing as big a circle as she can here
Let's go lure all the dinosaurs over here
Got it.
Look at that
Oh no.
That's the heat wave that exterminated the dinosaurs
Hurry up
Egg Expedition
Let's get these guys to help out too
Please.
This is not edible
But how do we get the dinosaurs to listen to us?
This is where we need to use that, isn't it Fat Tiger?
That's right.
Gere
Torp
You're here too, my friend of the heart.
I'm so glad you're all right.
Gert Torp
They don't understand what people say
They always listen to what their friends say, don't they?
Air Cannon
This way
By the way, if you make him smaller with the shrinking light
Shrinking Lamp
Why are all the cans of locusts
Doraemon
Oh no
Run, Kew!
Come this way
I said run, run, run!
Come on, come on, run, Kew.
This way! Come this way!
Come on, this way!
Everybody, this way!
Don't panic
Done
Please, just a little slower.
Do you want to keep reading?
At this rate their lives will be in danger too
Wait a little longer. Wait a little longer.
Kew
Come on, it's Khoo's turn this time!
Come on, Khoo, this way.
It's too dangerous. Let's get out of here.
Wait a minute. Look, the new dinosaur.
Come on, Khoo.
This won't work
Whether it's mu or something else like that
Neither will flutter their wings like that
It's okay, right?
With practice, you'll be able to fly just like Mew!
Kew, you can fly.
I must too
Someday
I'll definitely learn to flip the bar too
So, Khoo too
Don't give up so easily, Khoo too
Fly!
Fly Fly up
Go Go Go
Fly up, Kew!
Khoo!
Your name is Khoo
Flying up
Kew Flying up
Khoo So good
It's flying. You're not flying.
Here we go again
Oops, here it is
Where's Nobita?
Doraemon
Nobita
Watch me, this time for sure
Tinned Locusts!
Coming out
Nobita, just like that, flying straight over
Doraemon
Shrinking Lamp
Success Doraemon
Nobita, we don't have time. Get the crayons out.
After that, it's all yours.
Just go like that
Flying up
Flying up This is the moment of evolution
That awkward looking movement
Is that the precursor to soaring wings?
That's how dinosaurs once learned to fly on wings from gliding
Took the first step to evolve into a bird
We are now witnessing this moment of evolution
They didn't go extinct
but became birds to survive
If the boy hadn't been here
Guarding the words of that new dinosaur
The history of the earth may be about to change
Shizuka
Xiaowu Xiaofu
Pretty much all in one place
Still haven't connected with Doraemon?
Hey, little Dora.
Shizuka, how's it going over there?
Ready to go.
Do it!
It's burning.
Okay, ready to move.
Khoo, come on!
III
Running out of crayons
Saw it
Zero
Nobita, are you sure you don't want to say goodbye?
Saying goodbye will only make the separation more painful
It's our turn now. Let's go back to our time.
We'll always be good friends
Thank you, Topper.
See you later
Take care!
Don't come with me. You can't come with me.
You have to survive here
Be sure to stay alive
I'm sure you'll make it
Khoo, take care.
Miao Goodbye
Goodbye
Someday
We'll meet again
A Heart for Others
Perhaps this feeling is something that only humans have evolved to be able to produce
Like the dinosaurs evolved the ability to fly on wings
Humans have also evolved a wealth of emotions
Looking at them makes me think this way
Nobita
I can't keep sleeping in even if I'm on summer vacation
Get up!
It's turning over
Everyone, isn't it wonderful?
We'll see you next time